let savollar24 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "baggage",
      answer: "D. yuk",
      options: [
        "A. sumkani",
        "B. chantani",
        "C. quti",
        "D. yuk"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "bulb",
      answer: "A. lampochka",
      options: [
        "A. lampochka",
        "B. yong'in",
        "C. sokinlik",
        "D. nur"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "bundle",
      answer: "B. to'plam",
      options: [
        "A. guruh",
        "B. to'plam",
        "C. qatlamli",
        "D. dona"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "cattle",
      answer: "C. chorva mollari",
      options: [
        "A. qo'y",
        "B. ot",
        "C. chorva mollari",
        "D. echki"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to flee",
      answer: "D. qochmoq",
      options: [
        "A. yugurmoq",
        "B. sakramoq",
        "C. otlanmoq",
        "D. qochmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "to graze",
      answer: "B. o'tlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. o'rmoq",
        "B. o'tlamoq",
        "C. yig'moq",
        "D. ekmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "greed",
      answer: "A. ochko'zlik",
      options: [
        "A. ochko'zlik",
        "B. ragbat",
        "C. xohish",
        "D. intilish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "herd",
      answer: "D. poda",
      options: [
        "A. jamoa",
        "B. to'da",
        "C. qatlam",
        "D. poda"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to initiate",
      answer: "C. ishga tushirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. davom ettirmoq",
        "B. ochmoq",
        "C. ishga tushirmoq",
        "D. yaratmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "lane",
      answer: "B. yo'lak",
      options: [
        "A. yo'l",
        "B. yo'lak",
        "C. magistral",
        "D. aylanma"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "nerve",
      answer: "A. jasorat",
      options: [
        "A. jasorat",
        "B. qo'rqoqlik",
        "C. ikkilanish",
        "D. tinchsizlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "optimist",
      answer: "D. optimist",
      options: [
        "A. pessimist",
        "B. realist",
        "C. pragmatik",
        "D. optimist"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "parade",
      answer: "C. namoyish",
      options: [
        "A. marsh",
        "B. miting",
        "C. namoyish",
        "D. saylov"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to pave",
      answer: "A. tosh yotqizmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tosh yotqizmoq",
        "B. qoplamoq",
        "C. bezamoq",
        "D. yotqizmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "phantom",
      answer: "B. arvoh",
      options: [
        "A. soyacha",
        "B. arvoh",
        "C. xayol",
        "D. tuyg'u"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "portable",
      answer: "C. ixcham",
      options: [
        "A. yengil",
        "B. harakatlanuvchi",
        "C. ixcham",
        "D. qo'l bilan olinuvchi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "poster",
      answer: "A. plakat",
      options: [
        "A. plakat",
        "B. banner",
        "C. reklama",
        "D. e'lon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to scratch",
      answer: "D. qashlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. ishlamoq",
        "B. siljitmoq",
        "C. silkamoq",
        "D. qashlamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "symphony",
      answer: "B. simfoniya",
      options: [
        "A. opera",
        "B. simfoniya",
        "C. konsert",
        "D. sonata"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "widow",
      answer: "C. beva",
      options: [
        "A. ayol",
        "B. yolg'iz",
        "C. beva",
        "D. yosh ayol"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar24;